webprofits.com.au 2018-03-13

# Web Profits Digital Marketing Agency

## Privacy Policy

This privacy statement describes how Web Profits collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: [www.webprofits.com.au ](http://www.webprofits.com.au/) . It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

#### Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
  * Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences

We also collect the following information from you

  * Information about your business such as company name, company size, business type
  * Demographic information such as age, education, gender, interests and zip code

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Display content based upon your interests

###### Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [privacy@webprofits.com.au ](https://mail.google.com/mail/?view=cm&fs=1&tf=1&to=privacy@webprofits.com.au)

We enable you to create a profile, and share information such as messages, photos, and videos with others. Please note that we cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.

#### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, 
  * if Web Profits is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

###### Third Party E-Commerce Solutions Provider

Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions provider. They host our ordering system, and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. This company does not use this information for any other purpose. 

#### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.

###### Web beacons 

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

Our Web pages may also contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that are set by our third party partners. Web beacons are used along with cookies enabling our partners to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

###### Local Shared Objects - Flash Cookies

Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html>. 

###### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Web Profits. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

#### Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [privacy@webprofits.com.au ](https://mail.google.com/mail/?view=cm&fs=1&tf=1&to=privacy@webprofits.com.au)

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [privacy@webprofits.com.au](https://mail.google.com/mail/?view=cm&fs=1&tf=1&to=privacy@webprofits.com.au). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

#### Additional Policy Information

Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it. 

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

###### Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at [privacy@webprofits.com.au ](https://mail.google.com/mail/?view=cm&fs=1&tf=1&to=privacy@webprofits.com.au) .

###### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

Web Profits  
GPO Box 856  
Sydney, Australia 2001  
Email: [privacy@webprofits.com.au ](https://mail.google.com/mail/?view=cm&fs=1&tf=1&to=privacy@webprofits.com.au)  
Phone: 02 8806 6800
